Guide to The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings AIA.089
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings
1976-2001
1999-2000
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Flannelly, Adrian
Irish Radio Network USA
AIA.089
5.96 linear feet in 5 flat boxes and 2 cassette boxes
327 audiocassettes
Adrian Flannelly (born 1942) is an Irish broadcaster and the Chairman and CEO of Irish Radio Network USA. He hosts The Adrian Flannelly Show, a weekly radio program he began in 1969, which consists of a combination of music, international and national news, cultural news, economic analysis and commentary, as well as interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Flannelly has used his radio show to highlight social and political issues concerning Irish and Irish American communities, including United States immigration reform and visa lotteries. This collection consists of 256 audiocassette recordings of his weekly Irish American talk radio program The Adrian Flannelly Show, dated approximately 1978-2000. The collection also contains an additional 71 audiocassettes, dated approximately 1976-2001, whose affiliation to the show is unclear.
Scope and Contents
The Adrian Flannelly Show Recordings consists of 327 audiocassette recordings donated by Adrian Flannelly. The materials in the collection date from 1976 to 2001 with the bulk of materials dating 1999-2000. Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show contains 256 audiocassette recordings of Flannelly's weekly Irish American talk radio program, dated approximately 1978-2000. Flannelly's show consists of a combination of music, international and national news, cultural news, economic analysis and commentary, as well as interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Topics like immigration reform and conflict in Northern Ireland are discussed frequently. Series II: Additional Tapes contains 71 audiocassette recordings, dated approximately 1976-2001, whose association with Flannelly's radio program is unclear.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into two series:
Series I: The Adrian Flannelly Show
Series II: Additional Tapes
Within each series, the audiocassettes have been arranged in chronological order. Undated material was arranged in alphabetical order when possible.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Adrian Flannelly in March 2020; the accession number associated with this gift is 2020.020.
Biographical Note
Adrian Flannelly (born 1942) is an Irish broadcaster and the Chairman and CEO of Irish Radio Network USA. He hosts The Adrian Flannelly Show, a weekly radio program he began in 1969, which consists of a combination of music, international and national news, cultural news, economic analysis and commentary, as well as interviews with writers, musicians, politicians, and other public figures. Flannelly has used his radio show to highlight social and political issues concerning Irish and Irish American communities, including United States immigration reform and visa lotteries. He also serves as the Irish Cultural Liason for the Irish Hunger Memorial in Battery Park City, has received numerous honors from Irish and Irish American organizations in the greater New York City area, and in 2016 was awarded an honorary Doctorate degree from Quinnipiac University.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Appraisal
In 2021, 7 duplicate tapes were deaccessioned from the collection.
Radio programs.; Irish Americans -- Ethnic identity.; Irish Americans -- History.; Irish Americans -- New York (N.Y.); Irish Americans -- New York (State) -- New York -- Political activity.; Irish Americans -- Social life and customs.; Northern Ireland -- History -- 1968-1998; Peace movements -- Northern Ireland; Emigration and immigration law -- United States.; Radio broadcasters; Flannelly, Adrian
- The Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978-2000; 256 audiocassettes in 4 flatboxes and 2 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains 256 audiocassette recordings of Flannelly's radio program.
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, September 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0001)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, September 23-24, 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0002)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, December 1, 1978 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0003)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, April 30 - May 1, 1983 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0004)
  - Flannelly, June 4, 1983 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0005)
  - A. Flannelly Show, September 24, 1983 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0006)
  - A. Flannelly Show, October 8, 1983 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0007)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, October 29, 1983 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0008)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, November 5, 1983 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0009)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, December 3, 1983 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0011)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, December 10, 1983 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0012)
  - A. Flannelly, December 31, 1983 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0015)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 21, 1984 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0013)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 30, 1984 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0014)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 5, 1985 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0016)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 19, 1985 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0017)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 20, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0018)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 25, 1985 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0082)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 26, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0019)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 2, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0328)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 9, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0020)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 10, 1985 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0079)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 23, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0021)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 24, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0022)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 2, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0023)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 9, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0024)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 10, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0025)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 16, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0026)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 23, 1985 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0027)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 24, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0028)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 30, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0029)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, April 6, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0030)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show - No Guests, April 20, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0031)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, April 27, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0032)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, May 5, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0033)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, May 11, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0034)
  - A. Flannelly Show, May 17, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0035)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, May 18, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0036)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, June 1, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0037)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, June 2, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0038)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, June 8, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0039)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show (Gov Cuomo), June 15, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0040)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, June 16, 1985 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0041)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, June 22, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0042)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, June 29, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0043)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, August 3, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0044)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, August 25, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0045)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #2, September 1, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0046)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #4, September 1, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0047)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #1, September 8, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0048)
  - The Adrian Flannelly Show #3, September 8, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0049)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, September 21, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0050)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, September 22, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0051)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, October 3, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0052)
  - Adrian Flannelly, October 6, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0053)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, October 19, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0054)
  - Adrian Flannelly, October 20, 1985 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0055)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, November 2, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0057)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, November 9, 1985 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0056)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, November 16, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0058)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, December 8, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0059)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, December 15, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0060)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, December 22, 1985 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0061)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 11, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0062)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 19, 1986 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0063)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 25, 1986 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0064)
  - Flannelly Show, February 8, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0065)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 15, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0066)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 22, 1986 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0067)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0068)
  - Aircheck - Flannelly Show, March 1, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0069)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 16, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0070)
  - A. Flannelly, March 29, 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0071)
  - A. Flannelly Show Pt. 3, April 5, 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0072)
  - Flannelly Aircheck (11:30 pm - 12 Noon), April 5, 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0073)
  - Flannelly Aircheck (12 Noon - 1 pm), April 5, 1986 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0074)
  - A. Flannelly Show, April 12, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0075)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, May 3, 1986 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0076)
  - A. Flannelly Show, May 10, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0077)
  - A. Flannelly Show, June 28, 1986 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0078)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 1987 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0080)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 30, 1987 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0081)
  - A. Flannelly/Monsignor J. Murray, February 13, 1988 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0083)
  - Adrian Flannelly, January 2, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0084)
  - Adrian Flannelly, January 9, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0085)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 10, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0086)
  - Adrian Flannelly, January 16, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0087)
  - Adrian Flannelly, January 17, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0088)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 23, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0089)
  - Adrian Flannelly, January 24, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0090)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, January 30, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0091)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, January 31, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0092)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, February 6, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0093)
  - Adrian Flannelly, February 7, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0094)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, February 13, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0095)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, February 14, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0096)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 20, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0097)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, February 21, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0098)
  - Adrian Flannelly, February 27, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0099)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, February 28, 1999 (Box 1, Audiocassette 089.0100)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, March 6, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0101)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, March 7, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0102)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, March 13, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0103)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 14, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0104)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, March 20, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0105)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, March 21, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0106)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Sat Show, March 27, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0107)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sat Show, April 3, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0108)
  - Adrian Flannelly Sun Show, April 4, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0109)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 10, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0110)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 11, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0111)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 17, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0112)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 18, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0113)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 24, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0114)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 25, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0115)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 1, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0116)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 2, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0117)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 8, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0118)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 9, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0119)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 15, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0120)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 16, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0121)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 22, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0122)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 23, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0123)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 29, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0124)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 30, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0125)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 5, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0126)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 6, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0127)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 12, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0128)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 13, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0129)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 19, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0130)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 20, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0131)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 26, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0132)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 27, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0133)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 3, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0134)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 4, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0135)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 10, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0136)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 11, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0137)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 17, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0138)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 18, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0139)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 24, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0140)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 25, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0141)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, July 31, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0142)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, August 1, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0143)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, August 7, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0144)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, August 8, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0145)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, August 14, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0146)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, August 15, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0147)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, August 22, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0148)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, August 28, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0149)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, September 4, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0150)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, September 5, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0151)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 11, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0152)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 12, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0153)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, September 18, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0154)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, September 19, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0155)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, September 25, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0156)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, September 26, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0157)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 2, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0158)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 3, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0159)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 9, 1999 (Box 2, Audiocassette 089.0160)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 10, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0161)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 16, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0162)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 17, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0163)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, October 23, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0164)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, October 24, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0165)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, October 30, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0166)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, November 6, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0167)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, November 7, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0168)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, November 13, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0169)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, November14, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0170)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, November 20, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0171)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, November 21, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0172)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, November 27, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0173)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 4, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0174)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 5, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0175)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 11, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0176)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, December 12, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0177)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, December 18, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0178)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (1st Hour), December 25, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0179)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (2nd Hour), December 25, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0180)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (Hour 1), December 26, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0181)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows (Hour 2), December 26, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0182)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio New York, December 28, 1999 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0183)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, January 1, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0184)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, January 2, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0185)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 8, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0186)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 15, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0187)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, January 16, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0188)
  - Irish Radio, January 23, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0189)
  - Irish Radio, January 29, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0190)
  - Irish Radio, February 5, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0191)
  - Irish Radio, February 6, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0192)
  - Irish Radio, February 12, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0193)
  - Irish Radio, February 13, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0194)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, February 19, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0195)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, February 26, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0196)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, February 27, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0197)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, March 4, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0198)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, March 5, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0199)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, March 11, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0200)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, March 12, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0201)
  - Irish Radio, March 19, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0202)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, March 26, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0203)
  - Irish Radio, April 1, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0204)
  - Irish Radio, April 2, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0205)
  - Adrian Flannelly Show, April 8, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0206)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 9, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0207)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 15, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0208)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 16, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0209)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 22, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0210)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 23, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0211)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 29, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0212)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, April 30, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0213)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 6, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0214)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 7, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0215)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 13, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0216)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 14, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0217)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 20, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0218)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 21, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0219)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 27, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0220)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, May 28, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0221)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 3, 2000 (Box 5, Audiocassette 089.0222)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 10, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0223)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 17, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0224)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 18, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0225)
  - Adrian Flannelly Radio Shows, June 24, 2000 (Box 7, Audiocassette 089.0226)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, June 25, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0227)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 1, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0228)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 8, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0229)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 15, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0230)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 22, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0231)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, July 29, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0232)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, August 5, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0233)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, August 12, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0234)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, August 19, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0235)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, August 26, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0236)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, September 2, 2000 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0237)